

- ABOUT ME -

I am a constant learner, curious tech enthusiast and a natural optimist.

I am on a lookout for new opportunities, new places where I can fit, bring value and also grow and continue developing myself.

I am not afraid of challenges - in fact - I love them!

- TECH STACK -

I am playing around computers since my childhood.

Currently (since 2 years back) I focus on native Android Development in Kotlin. I would still consider myself rather a junior, however I learned a lot recently and I won't stop!

I have a hands on experience with clean architecture and MVVM.

I don't feel that confident yet to build a complex app from scratch, but if you give me a code of such app and ask to deliver new feature or a change, I can get my head around it quite quickly. XMLs and Compose, I can do both!

I went through several <mark>courses</mark> and <mark>books</mark> on Android and Kotlin.

I have also some knowledge of Python, C++ and website development from the past, so that all helps me to get well with coding principles.

REST API's, SQL, of course.

Previously I was an RPA Developer (for 5 years). I built software robots to ease from tedious repetitive work. It was awesome, but I needed a change, so I sailed to Android.

- WHAT YOU SHOULD KNOW ABOUT ME -

#### I am

- ... based in Czechia and I am open to hybrid/remote cooperation.
- ... currently employed, however still looking for new challenges.
- ... interested in remote cooperation..

#### I am

- ... able to speak fluently with 1.8 billion people
- ... capable of basic communication with other 0.5 billion inhabitants of Earth
- ... learning constantly to improve my language set, working on Swedish and Spanish.

# Thank you for your time!

Feel free to read to the next page for the "classic" CV!

# Roman Hruška

# **Android Developer**

#### Personal info

LocationBrno, CzechiaPhone+420 608 257 467Emailhruska.r@gmail.com

Date of birth 12/07/1992 Citizenship Czech

## Languages

Czech native
English fluent
Russian fluent
German intermediate
Swedish beginner
Spanish beginner

## **Computer Skills**

Kotlin 000 **Android Studio** 00000 **Python** 0000 C++/C# 0000 **UiPath** HTML **PHP** 00000 **CSS SQL** 00000 Javascript 0000 Eagle, Fusion https://github.com/roumenh

## **Personality**

Empathic Fast-learner

Humble

Honest

**Optimistic** 

**Positive** 

Problem solver

Self-motivated

Talkative

Team player

Versatile

### Others

**Driving license** A1, B – active **Welding course** (CO<sub>2</sub>)

### **Hobbies**

**Traveling** 

**Exploring the world** 

**Technologies** 

People, Friends

Hiking, biking, motor-biking

Woodworking
Guitar & keyboard

Music

# About me

I am technology enthusiast. I would say I am a life optimist and I believe that any problem can be solved. I really like challenges and learning new things. I like to have things organized and I like to share my knowledge with others.

As you can see below, my working history may look a bit unusual. I studied electro-technology. Then I switched to pedagogy. I taught teenagers for two years. I also run my own moving company for five years meanwhile. Then I learned about software robots and developed myself in it. The RPA itself gave me lots of experiences in tech field but I didn't have the chance to go deeper into programming which I feel like I am missing. Now I really wish to go deeper to coding than ever before.

Currently I am working as an **Android Developer** and I am eager and passionate to become very good at it and build some cool awesome apps!

https://g.dev/romanhruska / https://github.com/roumenh

# Work experience

#### **EMAN**

Prague, Czechia 02/2023 - right now

#### ANDROID DEVELOPER

- Development of new features using Kotlin, Clean Architecture, MVVM and other modern principles

#### **ROBOTICT**

Prague, Czechia 03/2021 - 12/2022

#### RPA DEVELOPER & DELIVERY LEAD

- RPA Development (UiPath) for various clients in UiPathGiving courses: RPA Development and Business Analysis
- Taking care of our Community, creation of educational
- Leading our RPA business unit

#### **ROBOYO SPAIN**

Barcelona, Spain 07/2019 – 11/2019

### **AUTOMATION ENGINEER**

- Software automation projects for variety of clients located worldwide using UiPath platform
- Complete development of automated processes: from estimation to production
- BluePrism fundamental training

# **KBC GROUP**

Brno, Czechia 07/2018 – 06/2019 and also 11/2019-01/2020

# RPA DEVELOPER

- Development of new robotic processes in UiPath Studio platform
- Management of robots and processes in shadowing and in production; BAU testing
- Overview of development life cycle, improvements in procedures, robot maintenance
- Automation of back-end administrative processes
- Leading an RPA training for other developers in group

## **SPŠ PURKYŇOVA**

Brno, Czechia 09/2016 - 06/2018

#### **VOCATIONAL TEACHER**

- Hich school teacher of practical education in field of electrotechnology

## SESTOPKOU.EU

06/2013 - 05/2019 Brno, Czechia

#### INDEPENDENT ENTERPRENEUR

- Moving and transport services. Household relocations

#### **WEBCENTRE.CZ**

01/2008 - 09/2013 Brno, Czech Republic

#### WEBSITE DEVELOPER

 Developement of approximately 20 websites using HTML, CSS, PHP & MySql

## Education

My secondary education is electrician and I have a bachelor degree in Pedagogy.